

SUMMARY

I'm a detailed people-first UX/Product Designer with six years of experience as a Product Manager. I excel at designing simple and effective solutions to complex user problems, relying on research and the company's business objectives to inform my decisions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX/PRODUCT DESIGN FREELANCER

New York, NY | March 2018-present UX research, strategy, information architecture, product design

Craft designs by applying design thinking principles throughout the design process to build empathic information architectures and prototypes.

Fully rebranded HORTŪS, a beauty salon in lower Manhattan.
Created new logo, labels for custom products. Redesigned e-commerce website in process.

DIRECTOR OF SALES MARKETING, SALES, AND COMMUNITY EXECUTIVE

Primary (Live Primary, LLC) | New York, NY | Aug. 2016-Dec. 2017 Coworking space with wellness amenities

Chosen as the company's first executive hire. Promoted to Director of Sales after demonstrating a strong ability to close deals and cultivate a strong community with a mix of established corporate companies (e.g., Pepsi), nonprofits (e.g., Kiva), and early-stage startups.

 Achieved 60% closure on leads and 93% office occupancy leading to a substantial increase in revenue.

PRODUCT MANAGER

babyMed | New York, NY | Sep. 2010-May 2016 One-stop online fertility and pregnancy resource

Developed and led an external team of developers, designers, and writers. Conducted usability testing and used findings to develop a taxonomy structure, content strategy, and full redesign.

 Increased pageviews 650% (to 12 million) and users 400% (to 2.75 million). All traffic was organic.

CASE PLANNER

SCO Family of Services | New York, NY | Oct. 2007-Oct. 2011 Voluntary not-for-profit human service agency

Managed a caseload of high-risk young men aged 17-21 years-old living in a foster care group home.

TOOLSET

UX DESIGN SKILLS

User Surveys

User Interviews

Competitive Analysis

Personas

User Stories & Flows

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Lo-Fi & Hi-Fi Mockups

Content Strategy

Typography

Color Theory

Branding

Usability Testing

UX DESIGN TOOLS

Sketch

Figma

Adobe Creative Suite

Invision

UsabilityHub

Maze

Balsamiq

Principle

FRONT-END SKILLS

HTML/CSS

Git/Github

Javascript

Bootstrap/UI Kit

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE, PRODUCT DESIGN

Bloc | Online | 2018

CERTIFICATE, TECHNICAL MARKETING

Startup Institute | New York, NY | 2015

CERTIFICATE, MEDIATION

Mediation Centre | Ontario, CA | 2010

BACHELOR OF ARTS, PSYCHOLOGY

Pitzer College | Claremont, CA | 2007